{
    "questions": [
        {
            "answer": "Generalized reinforcers",
            "options": [
                "Negative reinforcers",
                "Generalized punishers",
                "Negative punishers",
                "Generalized reinforcers"
            ],
            "question": "The tokens used in Token Economy are:"
        },
        {
            "answer": "Discriminative stimulus; Stimulus delta",
            "options": [
                "Discriminative stimulus; Stimulus delta",
                "Stimulus delta; Discriminative stimulus",
                "Punisher; Reinforcer",
                "Discriminative stimulus for punishment; punisher"
            ],
            "question": "When Raul asks his Math teacher for permission to use the restroom, he usually gets it. When Raul asks his classmate for permission, he usually does not get it. It's likely that the teacher will become a(n):___________________ and the classmate will become a(n):"
        },
        {
            "answer": "Continuous schedule of reinforcement",
            "options": [
                "Negative reinforcement",
                "Intermittent schedule of reinforcement",
                "Variable ratio 2",
                "Continuous schedule of reinforcement"
            ],
            "question": "Sally, a behavior analyst, is training a child to discriminate colors. She places a red card and a blue card side-by-side and tells the child 'Point to red'. Every time the child points to the red card, Sally gives her a bite of her favorite fruit. In this example, Sally used:"
        },
        {
            "answer": "Forward chaining",
            "options": [
                "Forward chaining",
                "Backward chaining",
                "Total task",
                "Backward chaining with leaps ahead"
            ],
            "question": "A BCBA task analyzed the skill of brushing teeth. The instructions were clear; the first step would be to teach the client to dry his hands and put the towel away. Which chaining procedure is the RBT implementing in this case?"
        },
        {
            "answer": "Least to most prompting",
            "options": [
                "Forward chaining",
                "Backward chaining",
                "Total task",
                "Least to most prompting"
            ],
            "question": "The tokens used in Token Economy are:"
        },
        {
            "answer": "Prompts are provided to avoid errors.",
            "options": [
                "The client is expected to commit errors during this teaching method.",
                "The responses are expected to be placed under extinction.",
                "Prompts are provided to avoid errors.",
                "Errors are punished with positive punishment."
            ],
            "question": "Which of the following statements is true for errorless teaching?"
        },
        {
            "answer": "Least to most prompting",
            "options": [
                "Most to least prompting",
                "Progressive time delay",
                "Least to most prompting",
                "Error correction"
            ],
            "question": "An individual was learning to ride her bicycle. Her father first assisted her with a full physical prompt. Gradually her father's assistance decreased its invasiveness. This example is an example of:"
        },
        {
            "answer": "Zero second delay",
            "options": [
                "Zero second delay",
                "Warning",
                "Reinforcer",
                "Physical prompt"
            ],
            "question": "Progressive time delay is always started with a:"
        },
        {
            "answer": "Non-Contingent reinforcement",
            "options": [
                "Fixed interval 5 min",
                "Variable interval 5 min",
                "Non-Contingent reinforcement",
                "Consequence manipulation"
            ],
            "question": "During a session, a client was presented with multiple Math exercises. The client was reinforced with a chocolate chip cookie every 5 minutes regardless of the behavior he engaged in. This is an example of:___________________"
        },
        {
            "answer": "Erase the number of checkmarks corresponding to the traded reinforcer",
            "options": [
                "Erase all the checkmarks",
                "Erase the number of checkmarks corresponding to the traded reinforcer",
                "Let the client keep some tokens to avoid problematic behaviors",
                "Add more checkmarks to the piece of paper to keep track of the transactions"
            ],
            "question": "An RBT is using Token Economy to reinforce following directions. The tokens are checkmarks on a piece of paper. Whenever the client trades his tokens for reinforcers, the therapist should:________________________"
        }
    ]
    "questionType": "Fourth and Fifth QUIZZ_ Chapter C Part I&II Skills adquisition",
  "questionID" : "4"
}